[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the first African American actress to win the Academy Award for Best Actress.", "correct_answer": "Halle Berry", "incorrect_answers": ["Diana Ross", "Angela Bassett", "Whoopi Goldberg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Union of Burma changed its name in 1989 to the Union of Myanmar.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Richard Gere, Terrence Howard and James Brolin starred in this 2007 movie about war crimes in Bosnia.", "correct_answer": "The Hunting Party", "incorrect_answers": ["The Brave One", "Up Close and Personal", "The Hoax"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This delectable chocolate dessert is named after fungi rooted out of the ground by pigs.", "correct_answer": "Truffles", "incorrect_answers": ["Nugget", "Eclairs", "Mushrooms"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Consider this infinite series: 1/2+1/4+1/8+1/16+1/32 +.... If we add all these terms, what do we get?", "correct_answer": "1", "incorrect_answers": ["3/4", "You cannot add an infinite series of numbers", "0"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What severed body part does Kyle MacLachlans character find in the beginning of the 1986 movie Blue Velvet?", "correct_answer": "Ear", "incorrect_answers": ["Tongue", "Head", "Finger"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these animals is a pest for the Garden strawberry, feeding on its fruit and leaves and transmitting various diseases?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Fruit fly", "Moth", "Slug"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where was the largest aquamarine stone found?", "correct_answer": "Brazil", "incorrect_answers": ["Jamaica", "Japan", "Iran"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1958, this man discovered huge footprints left by a mysterious creature around a construction site.", "correct_answer": "Jerry Crew", "incorrect_answers": ["Tom Slick", "Red Heart", "Bob Gimlin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In chemistry, this term refers to two elements with the same atomic number, but different atomic weights.", "correct_answer": "Isotopes", "incorrect_answers": ["Alleles", "Isochronics", "Isosceles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What part of the U.S. was hit by the North American Storm Complex of 1993?", "correct_answer": "East", "incorrect_answers": ["West", "South", "North"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these species has the most complex color vision known?", "correct_answer": "The Mantis shrimp", "incorrect_answers": ["The Tarantula", "The Bengal tiger", "The Great white shark"]}]